Guide to the Olga Rudge Papers Addition
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Rudge Family Papers, 1819-1991; Series III; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  - THIRD PARTY CORRESPONDENCE
    - H., George to Julia O'Connell Rudge, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 549)
    - Harris, Victor to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1911 Dec 16 (Box 14, Folder 550)
    - Howlett, Mr. to Mrs. Allanson, 1910 Feb 14 (Box 14, Folder 551)
    - Lasker, Robert S. to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1918 Feb 1 (Box 14, Folder 552)
    - de la Passeliere, C. de Neuilly to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1918 Dec 1 (Box 14, Folder 553)
    - Rudge, Arthur to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1917-18 (Box 14, Folder 554)
    - Rudge, Teddy to Arthur Rudge, 1910 Oct 2 (Box 14, Folder 555)
    - Rudge, Teddy to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1912, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 556)
    - Unidentified to J. Edgar Rudge, 1911 Apr 24 (Box 14, Folder 557)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Baynes, Ernest Harold, 1902-25, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 558)
    - Baynes, John, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 559)
    - Rudge, Edgar Marie, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 560)
    - Rudge, John Edgar, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 561)
    - Rudge, Julia O'Connell, 1890-1920, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 562)
    - Templeton, Peter Buchanan
      - Agenda, 1855-56 (Box 15, Folder 563-564)
      - Correspondence and copies, 1839-98 (Box 15, Folder 565)
      - Scrapbook, 1849-61 (Box 15, Folder 566)
      - Shorthand notebooks, 1865, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 567)
      - Printed material, 1819-85 (Box 15, Folder 568)
        See also: Oversize, Box 51, folders 1188-1194
      - Miscellaneous, 1864-68, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 569)
    - Miscellaneous, 1913-36, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 570)
- Photographs, 1902-1994; Series IV; 3.55; (9 boxes)
  Series IV, Photographs, is organized into eight topical subseries.
  - ALBUMS KEPT BY OLGA RUDGE
    - Album, 1902-69, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 571)
    - Album, 1925-28, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 572)
      Includes photos of Dorothy Pound's trip to Cairo
    - Album (Box 16, Folder 573)
      - Family and friends, 1962-63, n.d.
    - 2 small photo albums, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 574)
  - EZRA POUND
    - Ezra Pound alone, 1922-72, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 575-577)
    - Ezra Pound with Olga Rudge, 1965-72, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 578-580)
    - Ezra Pound with others, 1958-70 (Box 17, Folder 581-584)
    - Ezra Pound: funeral, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 585)
  - OLGA RUDGE
    - Olga Rudge alone, 1922-92, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 586-590)
      See also: Oversize, Box 51, folder 1195
    - Olga Rudge with hieratic head of E.P., 1975, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 591)
    - Olga Rudge with Mary de Rachewiltz, 1939-88, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 592)
    - Olga Rudge with Mary de Rachewiltz at E.P.'s birthplace in Idaho, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 593)
    - Olga Rudge with family, miscellaneous, 1984-88, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 594)
    - Olga Rudge with others, 1968-88 (Box 18, Folder 595-598)
    - Olga Rudge with others: Cambridge conference, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 599)
    - Olga Rudge with others: "Capri, early", [1921] (Box 18, Folder 600)
    - Olga Rudge with others: "Early Years", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 601)
      Includes photos of Egerton Charles Grey and Renata Borgatti
    - Olga Rudge with others: in Siena, 1953, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 602)
    - Olga Rudge: "photos set aside for biography", 1963-86, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 603)
  - FAMILY PHOTOS: INDIVIDUALS
    - Baynes, Louise ("Aunt Lou"), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 604)
    - "Polaris" (family dog), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 605)
    - Pound, Homer Loomis, 1929, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 606)
    - Rachewiltz, Boris de, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 607)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1925-85, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 608-609)
    - Rachewiltz, Michael Ezra de, 1982-86, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 610)
    - Rachewiltz, Walter de, 1949, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 611)
    - Rudge, Arthur, 1918, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 612)
    - Rudge, J. Edgar, 1917-21, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 613)
    - Rudge, Julia O'Connell, 1915, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 614)
    - Rudge, Peter, 1927, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 615)
    - Rudge, Teddy, 1917, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 616)
    - Vroom, Demian de, 1979-84 (Box 19, Folder 617)
    - Vroom, Patrizia de Rachewiltz de, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 618)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 619)
  - FAMILY PHOTOS: GROUP
    - Rachewiltz, Boris de, with family, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 620)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de, with family, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 621)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de, with Frau Marcher, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 622)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de, with unidentified, 1938-85, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 623)
    - Rachewiltz, Walter and Patrizia de, 1986, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 624)
    - Rachewiltz, Walter de, with family, 1982-86, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 625)
    - Rachewiltz, Walter de, with unidentified, 1983, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 626)
    - Rudge, Julia O'Connell with family, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 627)
    - Vroom, Demian de, and Michael Ezra de Rachewiltz, 1986-88, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 628)
    - Vroom, Patrizia de Rachewiltz de: wedding, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 629)
    - Vroom, Patrizia de Rachewiltz de, with family, 1980-86, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 630)
    - Vroom, Patrizia de Rachewiltz de, with unidentified, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 631)
    - Unidentified, 1981-83, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 632)
  - OTHER PERSONS
    - Antheil, George, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 633)
    - Awizus, Sabine, 1979-87 (Box 20, Folder 634)
    - Baira, Gabriella, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 635)
    - Baratti, Boris, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 636)
    - Bavier, Antoine and Gerlin de (Box 20, Folder 637)
    - Borgatti, Renata, 1921, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 638)
    - Briggs, Kevin, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 639)
    - Brooks, Romaine, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 640)
    - "Camile" and "David" (Box 20, Folder 641)
    - Casella, Alfredo, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 642)
    - Carpenini, Fernando, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 643)
    - Cavanaugh, Billy, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 644)
    - Chigi-Saracini, Guido, conte, 1953, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 645)
    - Connolly family, 1988, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 646)
    - Consolo, Ernesto, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 647)
    - Coover, Anne, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 648)
    - Cowrey Cuneau, Mabel, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 649)
    - "Cressida", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 650)
    - Eliot, T. S. (Thomas Stearns), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 651)
    - d'Erro, Civis, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 652)
    - Favai, Gennaro, 1963-64, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 653)
    - Fiona, Teodora, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 654)
    - Fitzgerald, Joan, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 655)
    - Foster, B. P., 1966 (Box 20, Folder 656)
    - Franchetti, Mimy, 1928, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 657)
    - Frazzi, Vito, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 658)
    - Hirzel-Langenham, A., 1939 Mar 6 (Box 20, Folder 659)
    - Höhs, Lisalotte, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 660)
    - Hughes, Robert, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 661)
    - James, Rebecca, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 662)
    - "Jean, Nina, Peter and Byron" (Box 20, Folder 663)
    - Johnson, John Alexander (Box 20, Folder 664)
    - Kahn, Perry B., 1918 (Box 20, Folder 665)
    - "Liza and Al" (Box 20, Folder 666)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh, 1982, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 667)
    - McKeown, Tom, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 668)
    - Mainerde, Errico, 1918-19, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 669)
    - Marinetti, Filippo Tommaso, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 670)
    - Mathes, Jim, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 671)
    - "Morrison", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 672)
    - Naldi, Nadia, 1934, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 673)
    - Naldi, Norah, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 674)
    - Overholser, Winfred, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 675)
    - "Padre Virgilio", 1950? (Box 20, Folder 676)
    - Peterich, Teola and Christophe, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 677)
    - Pia, Errico, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 678)
    - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1927 (Box 20, Folder 679)
    - Pound, Dorothy, 1963, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 680)
    - R.-, Mrs., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 681)
    - "Rossaro", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 682)
    - Rubin, Nathan, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 683)
    - Santoro, Jole, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 684)
    - Sarmiente, Olga Maria de, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 685)
    - Schneider, Jeanette, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 686)
    - Seeburg, Justice P., 1949 (Box 20, Folder 687)
    - Siena: Accademia Musicale Chigiana Festivals
      - Antheil, George, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 688)
      - Borgatti, Renata: mother, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 689)
      - Chigi-Saracini, conte, 1948-54, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 690)
      - Funeral attendee (Box 20, Folder 691)
      - "Marchesa Lenzoni", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 692)
      - Read, Forrest and Virginia (Box 20, Folder 693)
      - Unidentified persons and groups (Box 20, Folder 694-697)
    - Singh, Ghan Shyam, 1972, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 698)
    - Slavin, George, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 699)
    - Somers-Cocks, John, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 700)
    - "Stabili", 1951 (Box 20, Folder 701)
    - Thadeus, Nicola, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 702)
    - Traetta, T., 1952 (Box 20, Folder 703)
    - Umgault [?], Giuseppe, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 704)
    - Valsamacchi, Marie, [1914] (Box 20, Folder 705)
    - Wang, Lucien, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 706)
    - Whigham, Victoria, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 707)
    - Unidentified adults, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 708)
    - Unidentified children, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 709)
    - Unidentified groups, 1965, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 710)
  - PLACES
    - Bardi: "The Beach", 1943 (Box 21, Folder 711)
    - "Blunt's grave", 1966 (Box 21, Folder 712)
    - Bookstore L'Avocat, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 713)
    - Buildings, unidentified, 1966-83, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 714)
    - Chaumont-sûr-Loire, 1971-72 (Box 21, Folder 715)
    - Dordogne: Ezra Pound and Olga Rudge's walking tour snapshots, [1922-23?] (Box 21, Folder 716)
    - England: airfield (Box 21, Folder 717)
    - Ezra Pound's grave, 1974-79 (Box 21, Folder 718)
    - Gais, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 719)
    - Hailey, Idaho: 1985 Ezra Pound conference (Box 21, Folder 720)
    - Interior, unidentified, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 721)
    - Lago di Garda: headland (Box 21, Folder 722)
    - Lago di Garda: Sirmione Castle, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 723)
    - Landscapes, unidentified (Box 21, Folder 724)
    - London workshop of Henri Gaudier-Brzeska (Box 21, Folder 725)
    - Mestre: unidentified house, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 726)
    - Ogunquit, Maine, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 727)
    - Paris: Mabel and Ethel Duncan's apartment (Box 21, Folder 728)
    - "Penstone RA", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 729)
    - Portofino, 1926, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 730)
    - Rapallo, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 731)
    - Rapallo: Giardini Ezra Pound (Box 21, Folder 732)
    - Rapallo: grave of Homer Loomis Pound (Box 21, Folder 733)
    - Rapallo: "Lungo Mare", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 734)
    - Ruins, unidentified, 1984, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 735)
    - Sant'Ambrogio, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 736)
    - Sant'Ambrogio: Olga Rudge's flat, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 737)
    - Sant'Antonio: ruins, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 738)
    - Siena: Palazzo Capoquadri, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 739)
    - Siena: Palazzo Chigiana, n.d (Box 21, Folder 740)
    - Spoleto, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 741)
    - "Square Root's house", 1920 (Box 21, Folder 742)
    - Stamford, CT: "Baynes House", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 743)
    - Surrey, England: Effingham Church Cottage, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 744)
    - Tirolo: Castel Brunnenburg, 1946-57, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 745)
    - United States: unidentified house, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 746)
    - Venice: buildings, 1972-74, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 747)
    - Venice: 252 Calle Querini, 1973-87, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 748)
    - Venice: Cini Foundation (Box 21, Folder 749)
    - Venice: grave of Alexander Robertson (Box 21, Folder 750)
    - Venice: San Michele, 1973, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 751)
    - Venice: "tomb of John Harris", 1974 (Box 21, Folder 752)
    - Unidentified places, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 753)
      See also: Oversize, Box 51, folder 1196
  - MISCELLANEOUS
    - Animals, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 754)
    - Artwork, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 755)
    - Artwork: hieratic bust of Ezra Pound, 1972, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 756)
    - Artwork: images of Ezra Pound, 1920-81, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 757)
    - Dance and theater (Box 22, Folder 758)
    - Manuscripts, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 759)
    - Plaster masks of Ezra Pound and Olga Rudge (Box 22, Folder 760)
    - "Related to E.P.", 1980, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 761)
    - "Salons", 1922-69, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 762)
    - Negatives, 1925-30, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 763)
    - Negatives: glass, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 764)
    - Slides
      - Unidentified, 1972-74, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 767)
- Music, 1916-1995; Series V; 1.88; (5 boxes)
  Series V, Music, is organized into eight subseries alphabetically arranged by type of material.
  - ACCADEMIA MUSICALE CHIGIANA
    - Articles about, 1933-53, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 768)
    - Bulletino dell-Accademia Musicale Chigiana, 1951-60 (Box 25, Folder 769-770)
    - Calendars of events, 1979-82 (Box 25, Folder 771)
    - Calendars (ornamental), 1940-57 (Box 25, Folder 772)
    - Course information, 1955-82 (Box 25, Folder 773)
    - Invitations, 1958-78 (Box 25, Folder 774)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1950-82, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 775)
    - Notes, 1959, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 776)
    - Printed material, 1991, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 777)
    - Programs, 1939-63, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 778)
    - Publications, 1939-89 (Box 25, Folder 779-780)
    - Publicity, 1952, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 781)
  - ANTHEIL, GEORGE
    - Newspaper clippings, 1929-30 (Box 26, Folder 782)
    - Programs, 1989 Mar-Apr (Box 26, Folder 783)
  - CONCERTI TIGULLIANI
    - Newspaper clippings, 1933-38 (Box 26, Folder 784)
    - Publicity, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 785)
  - POUND, EZRA
    - Microfilm, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 786)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1978-83, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 787)
    - Notes by Ezra Pound, 1930, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 788)
    - Photograph, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 789)
    - Printed Material, 1922-83, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 790)
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Calendars of seasons and conferences, 1948-66 (Box 26, Folder 791)
    - Calendars of seasons and conferences, 1970-86 (Box 26, Folder 792)
    - Invitations, 1978-86, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 793)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981-85, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 794)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1921-87, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 795-798)
    - Organizations and associations, 1955, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 799)
    - Periodicals, 1928-85, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 800-802)
    - Programs, 1928-80, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 803)
    - Publicity for musicians, 1938-76, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 804)
  - RUDGE, OLGA
    - Announcements and programs, 1921-95, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 805)
    - Career notes and correspondence, 1916-62, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 806)
    - Notices and reviews, 1933-39, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 807)
    - Publicity, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 808)
  - SCORES
    - Beethoven, Ludwig von: Quartets, strings, no. 14, op. 131, c# minor, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 809)
  - VIVALDI
    - Articles, 1919-58, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 810)
    - Guggenheim application materials, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 811)
    - Microfilm, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 812-820)
    - Microfilm, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 821-827)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1938-85, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 828)
    - Printed material, 1946-62, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 829)
    - Programs, 1960-79, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 830)
    - Research Notes, 1930-47, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 831)
- Writings of Others, 1908-1995; Series VI; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  Series VI, Writings of Others, is alphabetically arranged by author.
  - Alberti, Luciano, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 832)
  - Alfieri, Vittorio, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 833)
  - Americo, Alfonzetti, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 834)
  - Antheil, George, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 835)
  - Appignanesi, Richard, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 836)
  - Auden, Wystan Hugh [W. H.], 1973 (Box 30, Folder 837)
  - Barfoot, Gabrielle, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 838)
  - Baumgarten, Fritz, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 839)
  - Bunting, Basil, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 840)
  - Chinellato, Gianfrancesco, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 841)
  - Christie, Agatha, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 842)
  - Chute, Desmond (Box 30, Folder 843)
  - Creagh, Patrick, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 844)
  - Cuchetti, Gino, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 845)
  - Dickey, James, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 846)
  - Dowden, George, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 847)
  - Duncan, Ronald, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 848)
  - Dupin, Jacques, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 849)
  - Eberhart, Richard, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 850)
  - Eliot, Thomas Stearns [T. S.], n.d. (Box 30, Folder 851)
  - Fasolo, Ugo, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 852)
  - Fuller, Buckminster, 1966-71 (Box 30, Folder 853)
  - Gallup, Donald, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 854)
  - Grinker, Morton, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 855)
  - H.D. (Hilda Doolittle), 1961 (Box 30, Folder 856)
  - Halle, Louis J., 1948? (Box 30, Folder 857)
  - Hecht, Anthony, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 858)
  - Hemingway, Ernest, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 859)
  - Herbert, Zbigniew, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 860)
  - Heymann, C. David, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 861)
  - Ionesco, Eugene, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 862)
  - Laughlin, James, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 863-864)
  - Lauritano, Giuseppe, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 865)
  - Lennard, Suzanne H. Crowhurst, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 866)
  - Levi, Primo, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 867)
  - "Libero de Libero", n.d. (Box 31, Folder 868)
  - McLuhan, Marshall, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 869)
  - McNaughton, William, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 870)
  - Malipiero, G. Francesco, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 871)
  - Montale, Eugenio, 1971-78 (Box 31, Folder 872)
  - Niehaus, Jeffrey, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 873)
  - O'Grady, Desmond (Box 31, Folder 874)
  - Pasolini, Pier Paolo, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 875)
  - Paulos, Peter, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 876)
    With cover letter
  - Pearce, Donald and Herbert Schneidau (Box 31, Folder 877)
  - Pevear, Richard, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 878)
  - Popa, Vasco, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 879)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1908-72, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 880-881)
    Includes draft of a limerick written in Capri, 1923
  - Pound, Ezra: typescripts and galley proof (Box 31, Folder 882-883)
    See also: Oversize, bsd, folder 1197 and Oversize, Box 51, folder 1198
  - Puccetti, Gabriella Bairo, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 884)
  - Quinn, Mary Bernetta, Sister, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 885)
  - Rainer, Dachine, 1973-75 (Box 31, Folder 886)
  - Reid, Ben L., 1965 (Box 31, Folder 887)
  - Saunders, Walter (Box 31, Folder 888)
  - Scheiwiller, Vanni, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 889)
  - Simms, George, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 890)
  - Singh, Ghan Shyam, 1956-65 (Box 31, Folder 891)
  - Singh, Ghan Shyam, 1966-95, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 892-894)
  - Sitwell, Edith
  - Smith, Keith Vincent, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 895)
  - Solane, Dominque Janine, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 896)
  - Spaulding, Maida, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 897)
  - Steiner, George, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 898)
  - Terenzio, Jacopo, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 899)
  - Torrey, E. Fuller, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 900)
  - Veronese, Francesco, 1978? (Box 32, Folder 901)
  - Vittorugo, Contino, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 902)
  - Wangerin, Walter, Jr., n.d. (Box 32, Folder 903)
  - West, Anthony, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 904)
  - Widershein, Marc Alan, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 905)
  - Wilson, Edmund, 1963-69 (Box 32, Folder 906)
  - Zacconi, Norma, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 907)
  - Unidentified, 1972-88, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 908)
- Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, 1918-1995; Series VII; 1.88; (5 boxes)
  Series VII, Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, is organized into three topical subseries and arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material within each.
  - EZRA POUND
    - Biographical sketches, 1926-87, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 909)
    - Book reviews - works about E.P., 1965-89, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 910)
    - Book reviews - works by E.P., 1929-87, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 911)
    - Brief mentions, 1928-82, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 912)
    - Conferences, exhibitions and commemorations, 1982-85 (Box 33, Folder 913)
    - Editorials and letters to the editor, 1937-88, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 914)
    - Essays and analysis, 1940-87, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 915)
    - "Gov't Case", 1973-77, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 916)
    - Interviews, 1968-86, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 917)
    - Music by E.P. - articles and reviews, 1973-83, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 918)
    - News articles, 1926-88, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 919)
      See also: Oversize
    - News photographs and other images, 1960-72, n.d (Box 33, Folder 920)
    - Obituaries, 1972-73, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 921)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-85, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 922)
  - LITERATURE
    - Auden, Wystan Hugh [W. H.], 1971-73 (Box 34, Folder 923)
    - Barilli, Bruno, 1938-54, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 924)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis, 1981-86 (Box 34, Folder 925)
    - Connolly, Cyril - articles by, 1968-74, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 926-927)
    - d'Annunzio, Gabriele, 1977-82, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 928)
    - Eliot, Thomas Stearns [T. S.], 1965-89, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 929)
    - Ford, Ford Madox, 1965-72, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 930)
    - Frost, Robert, 1971-74, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 931)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1973-74, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 932)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, 1962-85, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 933)
    - Huxley, Aldous, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 934)
    - Joyce, James, 1950-76, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 935)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1966-77, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 936)
    - Marinetti, Filippo Tommaso [F. T.], n.d. (Box 34, Folder 937)
    - Montale, Eugenio, 1975-82, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 938)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1972, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 939)
    - Nabokov, Vladimir, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 940)
    - Tornabuoni, Lietta - articles by, 1973-77, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 941)
    - Wells, Herbert George [H. G. ], 1973-76 (Box 35, Folder 942)
    - Wilde, Oscar, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 943)
    - Williams, William Carlos, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 944)
    - Woolf, Virginia, 1972-76, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 945)
    - Yeats, William Butler [W. B.], 1970-85 (Box 35, Folder 946)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1918-86, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 947-950)
  - OTHER SUBJECTS
    - American history, 1975-81, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 951)
    - Art and architecture, 1928-87, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 952-953)
    - Astrology, 1985-86, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 954)
    - Barilli, Bruno, 1938-77 (Box 35, Folder 955)
    - Biographical sketches, 1965-85, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 956)
    - China, 1965-78, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 957)
    - Cini, Vittorio, 1977-87, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 958)
    - Comics, 1985 Jun 23 (Box 35, Folder 959)
    - Education, 1963-77, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 960)
    - Fascism and World War II, 1928-85, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 961-962)
    - Film, 1968-85, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 963)
    - Fondazione Cini, 1979-81, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 964)
    - Health and medicine, 1920-85, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 965)
    - Human interest, 1928-85, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 966)
    - Italy, 1976-91, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 967)
    - Language, 1978, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 968)
    - Nature, 1970-81 (Box 36, Folder 969)
    - Obituaries, 1971-88, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 970)
    - Politics and economics, 1928-87, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 971-972)
    - Psychiatry, 1977-81 (Box 36, Folder 973)
    - Rachewiltz, Boris de, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 974)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1972-73, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 975)
    - Religion, 1926-85, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 976)
    - Rudge, Olga, 1919-95, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 977)
    - Science and technology, 1971-87, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 978)
    - Theater, 1964-86, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 979)
    - Travel, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 980)
    - Venice, 1969-87, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 981)
    - Miscellaneous, 1921-87, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 982-983)
- Printed Material, 1908-1991; Series VIII; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  Series VIII, Printed Material, is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Advertisements, 1941-89, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 984)
  - Announcements, 1972-91, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 985)
  - Art exhibitions and galleries, 1951-83 (Box 38, Folder 986)
  - Art reproductions, 1936-72, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 987-989)
    See also: Oversize, Box 52, folders 1200-1201
  - Beinecke-related, 1973-76, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 990)
  - Bibliographies, 1969, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 991)
  - Calling cards, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 992)
  - Dance program, 1986 Mar 12 (Box 38, Folder 993)